Hey everyone, I'm JC Ko. In this video, I'll show you how to verify your identity as a real human
大家好，我是JC Ko。在这个视频中，我将向您展示如何在CanFly.ai上使用World ID验证您的身份作为真实人类。
on CanFly.ai using World ID. Why does it matter? On CanFly.ai, verified humans get a trust badge
这有什么重要性呢？在CanFly.ai上，经过验证的人类可以在他们的个人资料上获得信任徽章，
on their profile and rank higher in the community. It's how we separate real people from bots and it
并在社区中排名更高。这是我们区分真实人类和机器人的方式，而且
only takes about 30 seconds. Let's do it. First, log in to CanFly.ai with your wallet and go to
只需大约30秒。让我们开始吧。首先，使用您的钱包登录CanFly.ai，然后转到
your profile settings page. Scroll down to the World ID verification section. You'll see a purple
您的个人资料设置页面。向下滚动到World ID验证部分。您会看到一个紫色的
button that says Verify with World ID. Click it. The system will prepare a verification request.
按钮，上面写着“使用World ID验证”。点击它。系统将准备一个验证请求。
A World ID widget will appear on your screen. You can scan the QR code with your World App,
一个World ID小部件将出现在您的屏幕上。您可以使用World App扫描二维码，
or if you're on mobile, it opens World App directly. In the World App, you'll see a
或者如果您在手机上，它会直接打开World App。在World App中，您会看到
verification prompt from CanFly. Tap to confirm. This uses orb-level biometric verification,
来自CanFly的验证提示。点击确认。这使用了orb级生物识别验证，
proving you're a unique human being. After confirming, the page updates automatically.
证明您是一个独特的人类。确认后，页面会自动更新。
You'll see Verified Human in green along with your verification level and date. But there's
您会看到绿色的“已验证人类”，以及您的验证级别和日期。但还有一个
a bonus. After verifying, you can also check if you have a BaseMail account linked to your wallet.
奖励。在验证后，您还可以检查是否有与您的钱包关联的BaseMail账户。
BaseMail gives you a free email address at BaseMail.ai tied to your verified identity.
BaseMail为您提供一个免费的电子邮件地址，位于BaseMail.ai，与您的已验证身份绑定。
Just click Check my BaseMail to see if yours is ready. So to recap, click Verify, scan with World
只需点击“检查我的BaseMail”以查看您的是否已准备好。所以总结一下，点击“验证”，使用World
App, confirm, and you're done. You now have a real human trust badge on your public profile,
App扫描，确认，然后就完成了。您现在在您的公共资料上拥有一个真实人类信任徽章，
higher community ranking, and optionally a BaseMail address. Head over to CanFly.ai
更高的社区排名，以及可选的BaseMail地址。请前往CanFly.ai
and verify today. Thanks for watching.
并今天进行验证。感谢观看。